Guide to the Franz R. and Kathryn M. Stenzel Research Files on Western American Art
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Research Files for an Unpublished Book on Western Art, 1859-1997; Series V; 9.66; (23 boxes)
  - RESEARCH FILES
    - Artist Information Index
      - Main File
        - Richter - Rix, 1906-67, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 423)
          October 1906 and January 1911 Pacific Monthly covers, with
          illustrated articles for Pacific Monthly
        - Roberts - Rollins, 1926-66, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 424)
          Roberts, Samuel H.
          Robinson, Charles Dorman
          Rogers, William Allen
          Rollins, Warren E.
        - Rorphuro - Runquist, 1956-71, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 425)
          Rorphuro, Jules J.
          Rossiter, Thomas Pritchard
          Rungius, Carl Clemens Moritz
          Runquist, Albert C.
          Runquist, Arthur
          Includes Christmas card from Carl
          Rungius with a print of a bear
          on the front, 1956
        - Russell, Charles, 1911-93, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 426-428)
          Includes photographic postcard
          of "Chas. M. Russell, 'The Cowboy
          Artist'" sent by C. W. Swearinger,
          Missoula, Montana, to Clinton
          Hiawatha Moore, Butte, Montana
          dated 1911 Aug 12
          folder 1591
        - Rutledge - Schaefer, 1948-74, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 429)
          Rutledge, Fred
          Rymer, W. C.
          Salisbury, Cornelius
          Salmon, Lionel
          Sandham, Henry
          Sanford, Henry
          Sargent, John Singer
          Savage, C. R.
          Savage, John
          Sawyer, Edmund Joseph
          Scammon, Charles Melville
          Schaefer, Harry
          Includes Guide to Game Birds by
          Edmund J. Sawyer, 1948 and an
          illustrated Christmas card from
          Ed and Helen Sawyer, 1963
        - Schafer - Scheuerle, 1885-1973, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 430)
          Schafer, Frederick Ferdinand
          Schatzlein, Charles
          Schell, Frederick D.
          Scheuerle, Joseph
          Includes Special Artist's Sale Catalogue by Frederick Schafer at Irving Hall...November 17th, 18th, and 19th, 1885 "
        - Schofield - Schoonover, 1965-67, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 431)
          Schofield, Socrates
          Schook, Fide de Forest
          Schoonover, Frank E.
          folder 1608
        - Schreyvogel, Charles, 1903-63, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 432)
        - Schroff - Scott, 1953-78, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 433)
          Schroff, Alfred Herman
          Schroff, Louise Barrows
          Schultz, Charles W.
          Schultz, Hart Merriam
          Scott, Julian
          folder 1592
        - Sears, Ben - Selander, Arthur A., 1963-67, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 434)
        - Seltzer, Olaf, 1941-71, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 435)
        - Seton, Ernest Thompson - Sharp, Joseph Henry, 1911-73, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 436)
          Includes Joseph Henry Sharp's
          cover for Montana the Magazine of Western History, Winter, 1973
        - Shattuck - Simons, 1961-75, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 437)
          Shattuck, Aaron Draper
          Shed, Charles D.
          Shirlaw, Walter
          Shope, Irvin "Shorty"
          Simons, George
        - Simpson - Smedley, 1960-69, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 438)
          Simpson, William
          Slight, [----?]
          Smedley, William Thomas
        - Smillie, George Henry - Smith, DeCost, 1888-1965, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 439)
        - Smith, Ernest Browning - Sohon, 1955-75, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 440)
          Smith, Ernest Browning
          Smith, J. D., Mrs.
          Smith, Jack Wilkinson
          Smith, Jerome Howard
          Snyder, Willard Poinsette
          Sohon, Gustavus
        - Spaulding - Stanley, [1929]-72, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 441)
          Spaulding, Elizabeth Hart
          Speil, George
          Spohr, Adolph
          Squires, Henry
          Stanley, Charles St. George
          Stanley, John Mix
          Includes "A Proposed Indian
          Portfolio by John Mix Stanley" by
          F. W. Hodge, reprinted from Indian Notes, Vol. VI, No. 4, Museum of
          the American Indian, October, 1929
        - Stein, Aaron - Stieffel, Hermann, 1960-71, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 442)
          Includes Hermann Stieffel, Soldier-Artist of the West by
          Edgar M. Howell. Contributions from
          The Museum of History and
          Technology Paper 12. Washington,
          D.C.: Smithsonian Institution,
          1960
        - Stobie, Charles Stewart, 1933-67, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 443)
          Includes Stobie's "Crossing the
          Plains to Colorado in 1865" and
          "The Charles S. Stobie Collection"
          both in The Colorado Magazine,
          Vol. X, No. 6, November 1933
        - Straus - Stuart, Granville, 1886-1968, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 444)
          Straus, Meyer
          Strobel, Max
          Strong, Joseph Dwight, Jr.
          Strother, David Hunter
          Stuart, Granville
          Includes two early catalogs of
          M. Straus' paintings, Easton &
          Eldridge, auctioneers, one dated
          1886, the other from September 8, 1882 [as dated in Schwartz, Ellen. Nineteenth-Century San Francisco Art Exhibition Catalogues (University of California, Davis: 1981).
        - Stuart, James Everett, [1903?]-66, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 445-448)
          Includes Catalogue of Oil and Water Color Paintings of the Yellowstone National Park, Idaho, Washington Territory, Oregon and California, by J.E. Stuart. Portland, Oregon, n.d.; Stuart's
          business card and stationery; an
          advertisement for Stuart's studio
          and typescript list of paintings
          by Stuart, 3543 entries by a
          dealer, with prices, n.d.
        - Sully, Alfred, 1963-65, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 449)
          folder 1593
        - Swaim - Symons, 1964-68, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 450)
          Swaim, Robert
          Swift, John Trankle
          Symons, Thomas W.
        - Tabor - Thompson, 1963-76, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 451)
          Tabor, Frank
          Tadama, Fokko
          Tappan, William Henry
          Tavernier, Jules
          Taylor, Bayard
          Taylor, Frederick Thomas
          Taylor, John Yeatman
          Terry, Eliphalet
          Thomas, Thomas Henry
          Thompson, David
          Thompson, Thomas Hiram
        - Throssel - Todd, 1956-75, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 452)
          Throssel, Richard
          Tilburne, Albert Roanoke
          Tobey, Mark
          Todd, Della
        - Toft, Peter Peterson, 1959-75, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 453)
          Includes "Peter Peterson Tofft:
          Painter in the Wilderness" by
          Robert Bigart and Clarence Woodcock
          in Montana the Magazine of Western History Vol. XXV, No. 4
          October 1975; a carte-de-visite
          photograph of Toft; an undated
          holograph letter to Holmes at the
          Cosmos Club from Toft
        - Tripp - Voorhis, 1963-70, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 454)
          Tripp, William Henry
          True, Allen Tupper
          Tucker, Alice
          Twachtman, John Henry
          Twiss, Lizzie
          Tyler, James Gale
          Valencia, Manuel
          Van Sloan, Frank
          Von Perbandt, Carl
          Voorhies, Charles Howard
        - Wachtel - Welch, [1927?]-64, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 455)
          Wachtel, Elmer
          Wachtel, Marion Kavanaugh
          Waddill, Mira C.
          Warre, Henry James
          Webb, Vonna Owings
          Weir, James Alden
          Weister, W. H., Mrs.
          Welch, Thaddeus
        - Wendt - Wheeler, 1934-77, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 456)
          Wendt, William
          Wentz, Henry W.
          West, Levon
          Westphal, Henry
          Wetteland, Sven Oftedal
          Wheeler, Mary Cecelia
        - Whistler - Wiggins, 1871-1965, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 457)
          Whistler, James McNeill
          White, John C.
          White, Nellie Reid
          Whiting, J. F.
          Whittredge, Worthington W.
          Wiggins, Guy Carleton
          Wiggings, Myra Albert
        - Wilkins - Wimar, 1886-1974, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 458)
          Wilkins, James F.
          Willoughby, Sarah Cheney
          Wilson, Charles Banks
          Wilson, Floyd
          Wilson, Jeremy
          Wilson, J. R.
          Wimar, Charles Ferdinand
          Includes "Indians of the Quinaielt
          Agency, Washington Territory" by
          C. Willoughby in Papers Relating to Anthropology, n.d.
        - Winter, Daniel, 1859-1967, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 459-460)
          Includes an albumen photograph of
          Winter
        - Wire - Woodville, 1908-97, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 461)
          Wire, Melville T.
          Wissenbach, Frederick Charles
          Wood, Alexander M.
          Wood, Charles Erskine Scott
          Woodbury, Arthur W.
          Woodley, C. W.
          Woodville, Richard Caton
        - Wores - Yelland, 1863-1973, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 462)
          Wores, Theodore
          Wright, Jennie E.
          Yelland, Raymond Dabb
          Includes three copies of Theodore Wores - Artist a pamphlet
          advertising Wores' work with a list
          of owners of his pictures, n.d.
          and Raymond Dabb Yelland (1848-1900) by Kent L. Seavey
          San Francisco: California
          Historical Society, 1964
        - Young - Zogbaum, 1885-1971, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 463)
          Young, Harvey
          Young, Mahonri M.
          Ziegler, Eustace Paul
          Zinstry, A. L.
          Zogbaum, Rufus Fairchild
        - Artists not fully identified, 1974, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 464)
      - Oregon Sculpture File
        - General file of information, 1974, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 465)
        - Clark - Fraser, 1928-71, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 466)
          Clark, Alan
          Clarke, John L.
          Cooper, Alice
          Dallin, Cyrus
          Fairbanks, Avard
          Fraser, James Earle
          Fraser, Laura Gardin
        - Kauba - Mora, 1906-63, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 467)
          Kauba, C.
          Koch, August
          Lewis, Alonzo Victor
          MacNeil, Hermon Atkins
          Mitchell, Jessie Lincoln
          Mora, Francis Louis
          Mora, Joseph Jacinto
        - Ostner, Charles - Perry, Roland Hinton, 1963, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 468)
          Includes Pioneer Idaho Artist Charles L. Ostner No. 10 of the
          Idaho Historical Series, November
          1966
        - Proctor, Alexander Phimister, 1935-94, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 469)
          Includes photographs of Proctor
          sculpting a lion, sculpture of
          General Custer, a fawn, and a buck,
          and a uniformed man (Proctor?)
          folder 1594
        - Roth - Wehn, 1953-75, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 470)
          Roth, Frederick George Richard
          Sawyer, Edward Warren
          Tilden, Douglas
          Warner, Olin Warner
          Waters, George Fitz
          Weaver, John B.
          Wehn, James A.
      - Alberta File
        - General Information, 1965, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 471)
        - Adney, E. Tappan - Armstrong, William Walton, 1964-65, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 472)
        - Bell-Smith - Brymner, 1963-69, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 473)
          Bell-Smith, Frederick Marlett
          Blake, Sara Mary
          Brigden, Frederick Henry
          Brymner, William
        - Campbell - Cross, 1964-67, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 474)
          Campbell, Robert
          Cartmell, Alban
          Challener, Frederick Sproston
          Copping, Harold
          Cross, Frederick George
        - Davies - De Grandmaison, 1959-65, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 475)
          Davies, Nora Drummond
          De Forest, Henry Josiah
          De Grandmaison, Nick
        - FitzGerald - Green, 1964-65, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 476)
          FitzGerald, Lionel LeMoine
          Garner, Alec J.
          Gissing, Roland
          Green, William Spotswood
        - Hagell - Hammond, 1964-65, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 477)
          Hagell, Edward Frederick
          Hall, Sydney Prior
          Hammond, John
        - Harris - Hutchins, 1958-65, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 478)
          Harris, Lawren
          Harvey, Reginald Llewellyn
          Hawksett, S., Jr.
          Henderson, James
          Hutchins, Edward J.
        - Jackson, Alexander Young - Julien, Octave Henri, 1965-73, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 479)
        - Kenderdine - Leighton, 1958-71, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 480)
          Kenderdine, Augustus Frederick
          King, Agnes Gardner
          Leighton, A. C.
        - Morris - Pursell, 1963-65, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 481)
          Morris, Edmund Montague
          Nevitt, Richard Barrington
          Phillips, Walter Joseph
          Prior, Melton
          Pursell, Lura Eva
          Includes The Frontier Art of R.B. Nevitt, Surgeon, North-West Mounted Police, 1874-78 exhibition catalog
          by the Glenbow-Alberta Institute
          [1974]
        - Roper - Sinclair, 1965-68, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 482)
          Roper, Edward
          Scott, Charles Hepburn
          Shackleton, Kathleen
          Sinclair, J. Gordon
        - Tempest - Winter, 1964-78, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 483)
          Tempest, John Sugden
          Verner, Frederick Arthur
          Watt, Henry Robertson
          Winter, William Tatton
          folder 1609
      - British Columbia File
        - General Information, 1964, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 484)
        - Adams - Atkinson, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 485)
          Adams, Edward
          Allan, William Mill
          Amess, Fred
          Anderson, John B.
          Angus, Lucy
          Arden, E. H.
          Atkinson, Sophia
        - Ballantyne - Bamford, 1963-65, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 486)
          Ballantyne, Alexander J.
          Ballantyne, Robert Michael
          Bamford, Thomas
        - Barff - Bullen, 1962-65, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 487)
          Barff, Lionel C.
          Barr, Patrick
          Beatty, John William
          Bedford, Fred G. D.
          Bedwell, E. P.
          Biddell, Percy James
          Bloomfield, James
          Brodie, George Staunton
          Bromley, Valentine Walter
          Brooke, Arthur A.
          Brooks, Allen
          Brown, Annora
          Brown, George Blair
          Bullen, Rose
        - Cameron - Cunningham, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 488)
          Cameron, Donald Stewart
          Carr, Emily W.
          Collings, John Charles
          Compton, P. N.
          Crease, Henry Pehring Pellew
          Crease, Josephine
          Crease, Lindley
          Crease, Mary Moberly
          Crease, Sarah
          Crease, Susan Reynolds
          Croasdailie, Henry E.
          Cunningham, Captain
        - Dallas - Fripp, 1963-67, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 489)
          Dallas, Alexander Grant
          De L'Aubiniere, C. A.
          Dufferin, Lord
          Eckler, Josephine
          Fairbairn, Archibald
          Fanshawe, Edward Dennys
          Fellows, Eleanor Caroline
          Fenwick, Cecil Godfrey
          Ferris, W.
          Frame, Statira Elizabeth
          Fraser, John Arthur
          Fripp, Charles Edwin
          Fripp, Robert Mackay
          Fripp, Thomas William
        - Haberer - Henson, 1962-64, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 490)
          Haberer, Eugene
          Hall, Edward C.
          Hamersley, A. St. George
          Hamilton, Lauchlan Alexander
          Hamilton, Mary Riter
          Harris, Bess
          Harris, Robert
          Hatton, W. S.
          Haverfield, J. T.
          Hedley, R. W.
          Heming, Arthur
          Henderson, Wilfred
          Henson, Percy
        - Herry-Celestine - Hurd, 1966, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 491)
          Herry-Celestine, Fanny Chislain
          Verhaeghe de Naeyer
          Hind, Henry George
          Hind, Henry Youle
          Hind, William George Richardson
          Holgate, Edwin Headley
          Holliday, Charles William
          Hood, Harry
          Hoole, Kate Smith
          Hope, Charles Edward
          Hopkins, Frances Anne
          Hughes, Edward J.
          Hurd, L. P.
        - Inglefield - Irwin, 1941-74, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 492)
          Inglefield, Edward Augustus
          Innes, John W.
          Irwin, D. T.
        - Jefferys - Kyle, 1952-66, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 493)
          Jefferys, Charles William
          Johnston, Franz
          Judge, Spencer Percival
          Kendall, E. N.
          Kingham, H.
          Kyle, John
        - Leather - Lort, 1965, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 494)
          Leather, Ethel
          Lent, D. Geneva
          Lismer, Arthur
          Lockerby, Captain
          Lorne, Marquis
          Lort, Ross A.
        - MacDonald - Marshal, 1963-74, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 495)
          MacDonald, James Edward Harvey
          MacDonald, James Williamson G.
          MacDonald, Murray William
          Mackey, J. R.
          MacLean, J. D.
          MacLure, Margaret C.
          Mallandaine, Edward M.
          Marega, Charles
          Marshal, J. S.
        - Martin - Musgrave, 1962, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 496)
          Martin, Thomas Mower
          Matthews, Marmaduke
          Mayne, Richard C.
          Mecham, George Frederick
          Menelaws, William
          Millar, Clara L.
          Milne, W. B.
          Moresby, Matthew F.
          Musgrave, Lady
        - Nash - Porcher, 1964-73, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 497)
          Nash, George V.
          Newton, A.
          Norgate, T. B.
          O'Brien, Lucius Richard
          Panter-Downes, Edward D.
          Parker, John Delisle
          Pearse, B.
          Pemberton, Augustus F.
          Pemberton, Joseph Despard
          Pemberton, Sophie
          Pinder, W. G.
          Pitts, Arthur David John
          Porcher, Edwin Augustus
        - Quentin - [Rowedewis?], n.d. (Box 27, Folder 498)
          Quentin, Rene
          Rand, Paul
          Rattray, Alexander
          Raworth, W.
          Richardson, E. M.
          Rithet, Elizabeth Jane
          [Rowedewis?]
        - Schellenberger - Uhthoff, 1952-66, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 499)
          Schellenberger, Otto
          Schofield, R. G.
          Sharp, G. L. Thornton
          Shrapnel, Edward Scrope
          Simpson, Charles Walter
          Somerscales, T. J.
          Southwell, George
          Sweeney, Lillian Clarke
          Thomson, Thomas John
          Thornton, Mildred Valley
          Tiedemann, Hermann Otto
          Tovey, George H.
          Tytler, Stanley
          Uhthoff, Ina D. D.
        - Van Empel - Vidler, 1962-65, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 500)
          Van Empel, Jan
          Varley, Frederick Horsman
          Vidler, Albert
        - Warre - Whymper, Edward, 1965-66, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 501)
          Way, Charles Jones
          Wellburn, G. E.
          Weston, Ellen
          Weston, William Percival
          White, George Harlow
          White, J. C.
          Whymper, Charles
          Whymper, Edward
        - Whymper, Frederick, 1962-66, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 502)
        - Willis - Wylde, 1965-66, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 503)
          Willis, Rose M.
          Willis, W. G. B.
          Wilson, Charles
          Withrow, D.
          Woods, Emily Henrietta
          Woods-Andrew, Helen Kate
          Wylde, Theresa V.
          Includes photograph of Rose M.
          Willis' studio
        - Young, Charles Warburton - Anonymous, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 504)
      - "Not Northwest" File
        - Aaris - Amick, 1961-73, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 505)
          Aaris, Hamilton
          Abert, James William
          Albrecht, Adolph
          Alcorn, Rowena Lung
          Allen, C. T.
          Allen, Thomas
          Ames, Joseph Alexander
          Amick, Robert Wesley
          folder 1595
        - Anderson - Austin, 1956-65, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 506)
          Anderson, Carl Thomas
          Anderson, Frederic A.
          Anderson, James A.
          Anderson, Victor Coleman
          Anderson, W. W.
          Andrews, Holmes
          Antrobus, John
          Armstrong, Samuel John
          Armstrong, Thomas
          Arriola, Fortunato
          Audubon, John James
          Audubon, Victor Gifford
          Austin, Charles Percy
          Austin, Darrell
          folder 1596
        - Bacher - Betts, 1953-65, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 507)
          Bacher, Otto Henry
          Bacon, Henry
          Bacon, Peggy
          Bagley, J. M.
          Ballou, Addie L.
          Bannard, John
          Barclay, Alexander
          Barker, George
          Barton, William J.
          Beard, James Henry
          Beard, Thomas Francis
          Beard, William Holbrook
          Beauchamp, Jack
          Bell, William A.
          Beller, August G.
          Benbart, E.
          Bensell, George Frederick
          Benson, Frank Weston
          Berghaus, Albert
          Berke, Ernest
          Berninghaus, Oscar Edward
          Berry, Karl
          Berry, R. S.
          Betts, Louis
        - Betz - Boyer, 1900-65, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 508)
          Betz, Bert
          Bigot, C. E.
          Bingham, George Caleb
          Birney, William Verplank
          Bixbee, William Johnson
          Blake, William Phipps
          Blatchly, William Daniel
          Blevins, W. H.
          Blount, J.
          Blunt, Simon S.
          Boal, James M.
          Bogle, James
          Boisseau, Alfred
          Bolmar, Carl Pierce
          Bonheur, Rosa
          Bosserman, Lyman W.
          Bouquet de Moiseri, J. L.
          Boyer, C. Philip
          Includes illustrated article on
          William Verplanck Birney by
          Pauline King in October 1900 issue
          of Truth
        - Boyle - Byxbe, 1960-73, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 509)
          Boyle, Ferdinand Thomas Lee
          Brader, J. C.
          Brayshaw, Thomas
          Brennan, Alfred Laurens
          Breuer, Henry Joseph
          Bridgeman, Frederick Arthur
          Brigle, William
          Broadhurst, Cecil
          Bromund, Cal E.
          Bromwell, Henrieta M.
          Brooks, A. F.
          Brooks, B. V.
          Brown, Benjamin Chambers
          Brown, J. G.
          Brown, Virginia
          Bruff, Joseph G.
          Bryant, Henry
          Bunner, Andrew Fisher
          Burr, George Elbert
          Burt, George
          Byrnes, W. S.
          Byxbe, Lyman
        - Cahill - Christofferson, 1960-1971, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 510)
          Cahill, Arthur James
          Caldwell, E.
          Calhoun, A. R.
          Callahan, Kenneth
          Calyo, Nicoline Vicomte
          Campbell, Albert H.
          Canoyar, P. S.
          Carlsen, Emil
          Carlson, [----?]
          Carrigan, William L.
          Casilear, John William
          Cassidy, Gerald
          Castle, James
          Castleman, P.
          Caylor, Harvey Wallace
          Chamberlain, Samuel
          Champney, J. Willis
          Chapman, John Gadsby
          Chinnery, George
          Choris, Louis
          Christoffersen, Gerda Gina
          Includes "An Early
          Nineteenth-Century Artist in
          Alaska, Louis Choris and the First
          Kotzebue Expedition" by James W.
          Vanstone from the October 1960
          issue of Pacific Northwest Quarterly
        - Christy - Currier, 1951-65, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 511)
          Christy, Howard Chandler
          Church, Frederick Stuart
          Clague, Richard
          Cleenworks, W.
          Cloudman, J. G.
          Clark, Alson
          Clymer, John Ford
          Coch, John
          Collings, H. A.
          Collinson, Richard
          Colomb, Christophe
          Colombi, Plinio
          Cookson, Stanley Alexander
          Cooney, Fanny Cory
          Cooper, Colin Campbell
          Corber, E. S.
          Coursey, R. Bigeon de
          Coutts, Gordon
          Coxe, W. H. M.
          Cram, Allan Gilbert